<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quotes_array">
        <item>"All things are delicately interconnected."</item>
        <item>"Calm is more conducive to creativity than is anxiety."</item>
        <item>"Categorizing fear is calming."</item>
        <item>"There is a space between stimulus and response wherein lies our freedom."</item>
        <item>"The body benefits from movement, and the mind benefits from stillness."</item>
        <item>"The darker the experience, the greater the opportunity for inner illumination."</item>
        <item>"Quiet the mind and the soul will speak."</item>
        <item>"In the end, only three things matter: how much you loved, how gently you lived, and how gracefully you let go of things not meant for you."</item>
        <item>"Attachment is the root of suffering."</item>
        <item>"Don't let your past determine your destiny."</item>
        <item>"If you want happiness for a year, inherit a fortune. If you want happiness for a lifetime, help someone else."</item>
        <item>"The man who moves a mountain begins by carrying away small stones."</item>
        <item>"There will always be rocks in the road ahead of us. They will be stumbling blocks or stepping stones; it all depends on how you use them."</item>
        <item>"The most common way people give up their power is by thinking they don't have any."</item>
        <item>"Everything you've ever wanted is on the other side of fear."</item>
        <item>"Happiness cannot be traveled to, owned, earned, or worn. It is the spiritual experience of living every minute with love, grace and gratitude."</item>
        <item>"Believe you can and you're halfway there."</item>
        <item>"I can accept failure, everyone fails at something. But I can't accept not trying."</item>
        <item>"I hated every minute of training, but I said, 'Don't quit. Suffer now and live the rest of your life as a champion.'"</item>
        <item>"Do what you can, with what you have, where you are."</item>
        <item>"Do one thing every day that scares you."</item>
        <item>"Life isn't about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself."</item>
        <item>"Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears."</item>
        <item>"If you can't fly then run, if you can't run then walk, if you can't walk then crawl, but whatever you do you have to keep moving forward."</item>
        <item>"You must find the place inside yourself where nothing is impossible."</item>
        <item>"Happiness is not a destination. It is a method of life."</item>
        <item>"Many of life's failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up."</item>
        <item>"In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on."</item>
        <item>"Wanting to be someone else is a waste of who you are."</item>
        <item>"Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony."</item>
        <item>"Your future depends on what you do today."</item>
        <item>"Speak only if it improves upon the silence."</item>
        <item>"If you want to change the world, start with yourself."</item>
        <item>"There are two days in the year that we cannot do anything, yesterday and tomorrow."</item>
        <item>"We are shaped by our thoughts; we become what we think."</item>
        <item>"The mind is everything. What you think, you become."</item>
        <item>"There are only two mistakes one can make along the road to truth: Not going all the way, and not starting."</item>
        <item>"When you arise in the morning, think of what a precious privilege it is to be alive—to breathe, to think, to enjoy, to love."</item>
        <item>"For success, attitude is equally important as ability."</item>
        <item>"The greatest test of courage on earth is to bear defeat without losing heart"</item>
        <item>"In this moment, there is plenty of time. In this moment, you are precisely as you should be. In this moment, there is infinite possibility."</item>
        <item>"Impermanence is a principle of harmony. When we don’t struggle against it, we are in harmony with reality."</item>
        <item>"The best way to capture moments is to pay attention. This is how we cultivate mindfulness. Mindfulness means being awake. It means knowing what you are doing."</item>
        <item>"If you want to conquer the anxiety of life, live in the moment, live in the breath."</item>
        <item>"Respond; don’t react. Listen; don’t talk. Think; don’t assume."</item>
        <item>"Mindfulness is simply being aware of what is happening right now without wishing it were different; enjoying the pleasant without holding on when it changes (which it will); being with the unpleasant without fearing it will always be this way (which it won’t)."</item>
        <item>"No matter how far out on the sea of suffering we’ve sailed, all that is required is to turn toward awakening. It’s never too late, but it takes that turning, and no one can do that for us."</item>
        <item>"Let go of the battle. Breathe quietly and let it be. Let your body relax and your heart soften. Open to whatever you experience without fighting."</item>
        <item>"Observing desire without acting on it enlarges our freedom to choose how we live."</item>
        <item>"Happiness is closer to the experience of acceptance and contentment than it is to pleasure. True happiness exists as the spacious and compassionate heart’s willingness to feel whatever is present."</item>
        <item>"The greatest satisfaction comes not from chasing pleasure and avoiding pain, but from the radical acceptance of life as it is, without fighting and clinging to passing desires."</item>
        <item>"With mindfulness we have the choice of responding with compassion to the pain of craving, anger, fear and confusion. Without mindfulness we are stuck in the reactive pattern and identification that will inevitably create more suffering and confusion."</item>
        <item>"Mindfulness is the energy that helps us to be truly present. When you are truly present, you are more in control of situations, you have more love, patience, understanding, and compassion."</item>
        <item>"Walk as if you are kissing the Earth with your feet."</item>
        <item>"People have a hard time letting go of their suffering. Out of a fear of the unknown, they prefer suffering that is familiar."</item>
        <item>"Letting go gives us freedom, and freedom is the only condition for happiness. If, in our heart, we still cling to anything – anger, anxiety, or possessions – we cannot be free."</item>
        <item>"Feelings come and go like clouds in a windy sky. Conscious breathing is my anchor."</item>
        <item>"Smile, breathe and go slowly."</item>
        <item>"Breathing in, I calm body and mind. Breathing out, I smile. Dwelling in the present moment I know this is the only moment."</item>
        <item>"Mindfulness isn’t difficult, we just need to remember to do it."</item>
        <item>"You yourself, as much as anybody in the entire universe, deserve your love and affection."</item>
        <item>"Meditation is the ultimate mobile device; you can use it anywhere, anytime, unobtrusively."</item>
        <item>"The difference between misery and happiness depends on what we do with our attention."</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="quotes_credits">
        <item>~ Holzer's Truisms</item>
        <item>~ Holzer's Truisms</item>
        <item>~ Holzer's Truisms</item>
        <item>~ Viktor Frankl</item>
        <item>~ Sakyong Mipham</item>
        <item>~ Natasha McKenna</item>
        <item>~ Ma Jaya Sati Bhagavati</item>
        <item>~ Buddha</item>
        <item>~ Buddha</item>
        <item>~ Confucius</item>
        <item>~ Confucius</item>
        <item>~ Confucius</item>
        <item>~ Friedrich Nietzsche</item>
        <item>~ Alice Walker</item>
        <item>~ George Adair</item>
        <item>~ Denis Waitley</item>
        <item>~ Theodore Roosevelt</item>
        <item>~ Michael Jordan</item>
        <item>~ Muhammad Ali</item>
        <item>~ Theodore Roosevelt</item>
        <item>~ Eleanor Roosevelt</item>
        <item>~ George Bernard Shaw</item>
        <item>~ Les Brown</item>
        <item>~ Martin Luther King, Jr.</item>
        <item>~ Deepak Chopra</item>
        <item>~ Burton Hill</item>
        <item>~ Thomas A. Edison</item>
        <item>~ Robert Frost</item>
        <item>~ Kurt Cobain</item>
        <item>~ Mahatma Gandhi</item>
        <item>~ Mahatma Gandhi</item>
        <item>~ Mahatma Gandhi</item>
        <item>~ Mahatma Gandhi</item>
        <item>~ Mahatma Gandhi</item>
        <item>~ Gautama Buddha</item>
        <item>~ Gautama Buddha</item>
        <item>~ Gautama Buddha</item>
        <item>~ Marcus Aurelius</item>
        <item>~ Walter Scott</item>
        <item>~ Robert Green Ingersoll</item>
        <item>~ Victoria Moran</item>
        <item>~ Pema Chodron</item>
        <item>~ Jon Kabat~Zinn</item>
        <item>~ Amit Ray</item>
        <item>~ Raji Lukkoor</item>
        <item>~ James Baraz</item>
        <item>~ Bonnie Myotai Treace</item>
        <item>~ Jack Kornfield</item>
        <item>~ Tara Brach</item>
        <item>~ Noah Levine</item>
        <item>~ Noah Levine</item>
        <item>~ Noah Levine</item>
        <item>~ Thich Nhat Hanh</item>
        <item>~ Thich Nhat Hanh</item>
        <item>~ Thich Nhat Hanh</item>
        <item>~ Thich Nhat Hanh</item>
        <item>~ Thich Nhat Hanh</item>
        <item>~ Thich Nhat Hanh</item>
        <item>~ Thich Nhat Hanh</item>
        <item>~ Sharon Salzberg</item>
        <item>~ Sharon Salzberg</item>
        <item>~ Sharon Salzberg</item>
        <item>~ Sharon Salzberg</item>

    </string-array>
    <array name="image_array">
        <item>@drawable/beach_stones</item>
        <item>@drawable/water_shimmer</item>
        <item>@drawable/wood_grain</item>
    </array>
</resources>